[
  {
    "question": "A house - two _____ .",
    "correctAnswer": "houses",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["housez", "an houses", "houze"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A chair, two _____ .",
    "correctAnswer": "chairs",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["chaires", "an chair", "chair"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A window, two _____ .",
    "correctAnswer": "windows",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["a windows", "windowz", "windowes"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A table, two _____ .",
    "correctAnswer": "tables",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["a tables", "tabls", "tablez"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A door, two _____ .",
    "correctAnswer": "doors",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["a doors", "doores", "doorez"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A dog, two _____ .",
    "correctAnswer": "dogs",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["a dogs", "dogz", "doges"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A cat, two _____ .",
    "correctAnswer": "cats",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["a cats", "cates", "catz"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A rabbit, two _____ .",
    "correctAnswer": "rabbits",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["a rabbits", "rabbites", "rabbities"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A hamster, two _____ .",
    "correctAnswer": "hamsters",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["a hamsters", "hamsterz", "hamsteres"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A parrot, two _____ .",
    "correctAnswer": "parrots",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["a parrots", "parrotes", "parrotz"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A bear, two _____ .",
    "correctAnswer": "bears",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["a bears", "beares", "bearz"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A wolf, two _____ .",
    "correctAnswer": "wolves",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["a wolves", "wolfs", "wolvez"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A fox, two _____ .",
    "correctAnswer": "foxes",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["a foxes", "foxs", "foxez"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A monkey, two _____ .",
    "correctAnswer": "monkeys",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["a monkeys", "monkeis", "monkeyz"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A lion, two _____ .",
    "correctAnswer": "lions",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["a lions", "liAs", "lionz"]
  },
  {
    "question": "An elephant, two _____ .",
    "correctAnswer": "elephants",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["an elephants", "a elephant", "elephantz"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A giraffe, two _____ .",
    "correctAnswer": "giraffes",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["a giraffes", "giraffs", "giraffez"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A shark, two _____ .",
    "correctAnswer": "sharks",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["a sharks", "sharkis", "sharkies"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A dolphin, two _____ .",
    "correctAnswer": "dolphins",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["a dolphins", "dolphines", "dolphinez"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A turtle, two _____ .",
    "correctAnswer": "turtles",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["a turtles", "an turtle", "turtls"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A car, two _____ .",
    "correctAnswer": "cars",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["a cars", "cares", "carz"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A doll, two _____ .",
    "correctAnswer": "dolls",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["a dolls", "dolles", "dollz"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A ball, two _____ .",
    "correctAnswer": "balls",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["a balls", "balles", "ballz"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A robot, two _____ .",
    "correctAnswer": "robots",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["a robots", "roboties", "robotes"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A teddy, two _____ .",
    "correctAnswer": "teddies",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["a teddies", "teddys", "teddyz"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A clown, two _____ .",
    "correctAnswer": "clowns",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["a clowns", "clownes", "clownez"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A plane, two _____ .",
    "correctAnswer": "planes",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["a planes", "planeis", "planez"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A computer, two _____ .",
    "correctAnswer": "computers",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["a computers", "computeres", "computerz"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A balloon, two _____ .",
    "correctAnswer": "balloons",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["a balloons", "balloonz", "balloAs"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A present, two _____ .",
    "correctAnswer": "presents",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["a presents", "presentes", "presentz"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A kite, two _____ .",
    "correctAnswer": "kites",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["a kites", "kits", "kities"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A scooter, two _____ .",
    "correctAnswer": "scooters",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["a scooters", "scooteres", "scooterz"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A train, two _____ .",
    "correctAnswer": "trains",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["a trains", "traines", "trainez"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A bike, two _____ .",
    "correctAnswer": "bikes",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["a bikes", "biks", "bikez"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A head, two _____ .",
    "correctAnswer": "heads",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["a heads", "heades", "headz"]
  },
  {
    "question": "An eye, two _____ .",
    "correctAnswer": "eyes",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["an eyes", "eyeis", "eyez"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A nose, two _____ .",
    "correctAnswer": "noses",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["a noses", "nosez", "nosies"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A mouth, two _____ .",
    "correctAnswer": "mouths",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["a mouths", "mouthes", "mouthez"]
  },
  {
    "question": "An ear, two _____ .",
    "correctAnswer": "ears",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["an ears", "eares", "earz"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A tooth, two _____ .",
    "correctAnswer": "teeth",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["a teeth", "toothes", "tooths"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A face, two _____ .",
    "correctAnswer": "faces",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["a faces", "facez", "facies"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A snowman, two _____ .",
    "correctAnswer": "snowmen",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["a snowmen", "snowmens", "snowsmen"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A snowball, two _____ .",
    "correctAnswer": "snowballs",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["a snowballs", "snowsball", "snowballes"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A cloud, two _____ .",
    "correctAnswer": "clouds",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["a clouds", "cloudes", "cloudez"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A star, two _____ .",
    "correctAnswer": "stars",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["a stars", "starz", "staries"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A jacket, two _____ .",
    "correctAnswer": "jackets",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["a jackets", "jacketis", "jacketz"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A T-shirt, two _____ .",
    "correctAnswer": "T-shirts",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["a T-shirts", "tes-shirt", "T-shirties"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A sock, two _____ .",
    "correctAnswer": "socks",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["a sock", "sockes", "sockz"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A shoe, two _____ .",
    "correctAnswer": "shoes",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["a shoes", "shoees", "shoies"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A glove, two _____ .",
    "correctAnswer": "gloves",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["a gloves", "glovs", "glofes"]
  },
  {
    "question": "An umbrella, two _____ .",
    "correctAnswer": "umbrellas",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["an umbrellas", "umbrellaes", "umbrellaz"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A hat, two _____ .",
    "correctAnswer": "hats",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["a hats", "hattes", "hatts"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A scarf, two _____ .",
    "correctAnswer": "scarves",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["a scarves", "scarffes", "scarfs"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A apple, two _____ .",
    "correctAnswer": "apples",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["an apples", "appls", "applez"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A banana, two _____ .",
    "correctAnswer": "bananas",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["a bananas", "bananaes", "bananaz"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A lemon, two _____ .",
    "correctAnswer": "lemons",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["a lemons", "lemonz", "lemones"]
  },
  {
    "question": "An orange, two _____ .",
    "correctAnswer": "oranges",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["an oranges", "orangees", "orangies"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A pear, two _____ .",
    "correctAnswer": "pears",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["a pears", "peares", "pearz"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Two cucumbers, one _____ .",
    "correctAnswer": "cucumber",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["cukumber", "an cucumber", "cucumberes"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Two tomatoes, one _____ .",
    "correctAnswer": "tomato",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["tomatoe", "an tomato", "tomatos"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Two potatoes, one _____ .",
    "correctAnswer": "potato",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["potatoe", "an potato", "potatos"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Two carrots, one _____ .",
    "correctAnswer": "carrot",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["carot", "an carrot", "carrotes"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Two cakes, one _____ .",
    "correctAnswer": "cake",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["kace", "an cake", "caks"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Two drinks, one _____ .",
    "correctAnswer": "drink",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["drinc", "an drink", "drinkes"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Two biscuits, one _____ .",
    "correctAnswer": "biscuit",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["biskuit", "an biscuit", "biscuitues"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Two sandwiches, one _____ .",
    "correctAnswer": "sandwich",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["sandvich", "an sandwich", "sandwichs"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Two ice creams, one _____ .",
    "correctAnswer": "ice cream",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["ise cream", "a ice cream", "ices cream"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Two buses, one _____ .",
    "correctAnswer": "bus",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["bas", "an bus", "buss"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Two ships, one _____ .",
    "correctAnswer": "ship",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["shep", "an ship", "shippes"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Two boats, one _____ .",
    "correctAnswer": "boat",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["bote", "an boat", "boates"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Two tickets, one _____ .",
    "correctAnswer": "ticket",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["tiket", "an ticket", "ticketz"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Two airports, one _____ .",
    "correctAnswer": "airport",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["airporte", "a airport", "airporttes"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Two dresses, one _____ .",
    "correctAnswer": "dress",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["dres", "an dress", "dressis"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Two colours, one _____ .",
    "correctAnswer": "colour",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["kolour", "an colour", "coloures"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Two mothers, one _____ .",
    "correctAnswer": "mother",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["mather", "an mother", "motheres"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Two fathers, one _____ .",
    "correctAnswer": "father",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["fathe", "an father", "fatherz"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Two sisters, one _____ .",
    "correctAnswer": "sister",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["sester", "an sister", "sisterz"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Two brothers, one _____ .",
    "correctAnswer": "brother",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["brather", "an brother", "brotheres"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Two daughters, one _____ .",
    "correctAnswer": "daughter",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["doghter", "an daughter", "daughteres"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Two sons, one _____ .",
    "correctAnswer": "son",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["sun", "an son", "sonz"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Two parents, one _____ .",
    "correctAnswer": "parent",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["pearent", "an parent", "parentes"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Two families, one _____ .",
    "correctAnswer": "family",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["famile", "an family", "familys"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Two members, one _____ .",
    "correctAnswer": "member",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["membere", "an member", "memberes"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Two grandmothers, one _____ .",
    "correctAnswer": "grandmother",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["grandmather", "an grandmother", "grandsmother"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Two grandfathers, one _____ .",
    "correctAnswer": "grandfather",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["grandfathere", "an grandfather", "grandfatheres"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Two men, one _____ .",
    "correctAnswer": "man",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["mene", "an man", "mans"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Two women, one _____ .",
    "correctAnswer": "woman",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["womane", "an woman", "womans"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Two boys, one _____ .",
    "correctAnswer": "boy",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["boi", "an boy", "boies"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Two girls, one _____ .",
    "correctAnswer": "girl",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["girle", "an girl", "girlz"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Two flats, one _____ .",
    "correctAnswer": "flat",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["phlat", "an flat", "flates"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Two rooms, one _____ .",
    "correctAnswer": "room",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["roome", "an room", "romes"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Two floors, one _____ .",
    "correctAnswer": "floor",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["flor", "an floor", "floores"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Two bedrooms, one _____ .",
    "correctAnswer": "bedroom",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["badroom", "an bedroom", "bedsrooms"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Two pets, one _____ .",
    "correctAnswer": "pet",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["pat", "an pet", "pat"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Two airports, one _____ .",
    "correctAnswer": "airport",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["airporte", "a airport", "airporttes"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Two seas, one _____ .",
    "correctAnswer": "sea",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["see", "an sea", "seaz"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Two rivers, one _____ .",
    "correctAnswer": "river",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["rever", "an river", "riveries"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Two oceans, one _____ .",
    "correctAnswer": "ocean",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["oceane", "an ocean", "oceanz"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Two games, one _____ .",
    "correctAnswer": "game",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["geime", "an game", "gamies"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Two toys, one _____ .",
    "correctAnswer": "toy",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["toi", "an toy", "toies"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Two puzzles, one _____ .",
    "correctAnswer": "puzzle",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["puzl", "an puzzle", "puzzlez"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Two mornings, one _____ .",
    "correctAnswer": "morning",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["morninge", "an morning", "morningz"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Two days, one _____ .",
    "correctAnswer": "day",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["dai", "an day", "daies"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Two evenings, one _____ .",
    "correctAnswer": "evening",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["evining", "a evening", "eveningz"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Two nights, one _____ .",
    "correctAnswer": "night",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["nite", "an night", "nightz"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Two weeks, one _____ .",
    "correctAnswer": "week",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["wik", "an week", "weekz"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Two months, one _____ .",
    "correctAnswer": "month",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["manth", "an month", "monthes"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Two gardens, one _____ .",
    "correctAnswer": "garden",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["gardene", "an garden", "gardenz"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Two breakfasts, one _____ .",
    "correctAnswer": "breakfast",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["brekfast", "an breakfast", "breakfastz"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Two dinners, one _____ .",
    "correctAnswer": "dinner",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["diner", "an dinner", "dinneres"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Two lunches, one _____ .",
    "correctAnswer": "lunch",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["lanch", "an lunch", "lunchez"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Two snacks, one _____ .",
    "correctAnswer": "snack",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["snak", "an snack", "snackes"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Two trips, one _____ .",
    "correctAnswer": "trip",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["tripe", "an trip", "tripz"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Two holidays, one _____ .",
    "correctAnswer": "holiday",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["holidai", "an holiday", "holidaies"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Two smiles, one _____ .",
    "correctAnswer": "smile",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["smale", "an smile", "smils"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Two hens, one _____ .",
    "correctAnswer": "hen",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["han", "an hen", "henes"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Two caps, one _____ .",
    "correctAnswer": "cap",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["kap", "an cap", "capes"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Two ducks, one _____ .",
    "correctAnswer": "duck",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["duk", "an duck", "duckz"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Two beds, one _____ .",
    "correctAnswer": "bed",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["bad", "an bed", "bedz"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Two letters, one _____ .",
    "correctAnswer": "letter",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["leter", "an letter", "letterz"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Two phones, one _____ .",
    "correctAnswer": "phone",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["fone", "an phone", "phonez"]
  }
]